Finding Aid for the Recordings of Creative Associates Recitals, 1964-1980
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Reel to reel tapes, 1964-1980, I.; Reel 1-Reel 172
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 14, November 28, 1966, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 3, Reel 028-029)
    Work number: ubmu0063_028_01
    Karlins, Martin William
    Solo piece for Clarinet (1964)
    Performers: Paul Zonn, clarinet
    Duration: 3:50
    Cassette backup: CA 088
    Note: Listed on original program as 3rd work, engineer notes reordering.
    Note: Order of works changed from program as 3, 4, 1, 2 - check
    Work number: ubmu0063_028_02
    Music for Oboe, Bass Clarinet and piano (1966)
    Performers: Wilma Zonn, oboe; Paul Zonn, bass clarinet; Carlos Roque Alsina, piano
    Duration: 6:33
    Cassette backup: CA 089
    Note: Listed on original program as 4th work, engineer notes reordering.
    Work number: ubmu0063_028_03
    Castiglioni, Niccolo
    Alleluja Solo (1966)
    Performers: Shaul Ben Meir, flute
    Duration: 2:43
    Cassette backup: CA 090
    Note: Listed on original program as 1st work, engineer notes reordering.
    Work number: ubmu0063_028_04
    Gymel (1960)
    Performers: Shaul Ben Meir, flute; Niccolo Castiglioni, piano
    Duration: 5:03
    Cassette backup: CA 091
    Note: Listed on original program as 2nd work, engineer notes reordering.
    Work number: ubmu0063_029_01
    Zonn, Paul
    Three Folk Songs on Stephen Crane (1960)
    Performers: Anne Graff, contralto; Cornelius Cardew, piano
    Duration: 5:35
    Cassette backup: CA 092
    Work number: ubmu0063_029_02
    Periphrasis (1966)
    Performers: Wilma Zonn, oboe; Paul Zonn, clarinet; Robert Martin, violoncello
    Duration: 6:40
    Cassette backup: CA 093
    Work number: ubmu0063_029_03
    Madrigal: "I Love My Lady" (1966)
    Performers: John Thomas, Warren Hoffer, Laurence Bogue, tenors; Paul Zonn, Andrew White, Richard Dufallo, clarinets
    Duration: 4:44
    Cassette backup: CA 094
    Work number: ubmu0063_029_04
    Cardew, Cornelius
    Solo with Accompaniment (1964)
    Performers: Robert Martin, violoncello; Cornelius Cardew, piano
    Duration: 9:03
    Cassette backup: CA 095
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 15, December 7, 1966, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 3, Reel 030-031)
    Work number: ubmu0063_030_01
    Chamber piece for percussion Quintet (1954)
    Performers: U.B. Percussion Ensemble
    Duration: 7:19
    Cassette backup: CA 099
    Work number: ubmu0063_030_02
    Brahms, Johannes
    Trio, piano, clarinet, violoncello, op. 114, A minor
    Performers: Paul Zonn, clarinet; Robert Martin, violoncello; Carlos Roque Alsina, piano
    Duration: 22:07
    Cassette backup: CA 100
    Work number: ubmu0063_031_01
    Sonata, viola (1964)
    Performers: Jean Dupouy, viola
    Duration: 7:35
    Cassette backup: CA 097
    Work number: ubmu0063_031_02
    Carter, Elliott
    Etudes and a fantasy, woodwinds
    Performers: Shaul Ben Meir, flute; Wilma Zonn, oboe; Paul Zonn, clarinet; Darlene Reynard, bassoon
    Duration: 16:47
    Cassette backup: CA 098
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 16, January 14, 1967, 1 10-inch reel; Full-track mono, 15 ips (Box 3, Reel 032)
    Work number: ubmu0063_032_01
    Vivaldi, Antonio
    Gloria, D major. Domine Deus, Agnus Dei
    Performers: Anne Graff, contralto; David Garvey, piano
    Duration: 3:46
    Cassette backup: CA 101
    Work number: ubmu0063_032_02
    Beethoven, Ludwig van
    Vom Tode, op. 48, no. 3
    Duration: 2:28
    Cassette backup: CA 102
    Work number: ubmu0063_032_03
    Nachtigall, op. 97, no. 1
    Duration: 2:11
    Cassette backup: CA 103
    Work number: ubmu0063_032_04
    Wie Melodien zieht es mir, op. 105, no. 1
    Duration: 4:39
    Cassette backup: CA 104
    Work number: ubmu0063_032_05
    Schubert, Franz
    Erlkönig, D. 328
    Performers: Ann Graff, contralto; David Garvey, piano
    Cassette backup: CA 105
    Work number: ubmu0063_032_06
    Menotti, Gian-Carlo
    Medium. Madame Flora Afraid?
    Cassette backup: CA 106
    Work number: ubmu0063_032_07
    French Traditional, arranged by Weckerlin
    Les Quinze Ans de Rosette; Au Bord de la Fontaine
    Duration: 3:22
    Cassette backup: CA 107
    Work number: ubmu0063_032_08
    Gershwin, George
    Porgy and Bess. Summertime
    Duration: 2:13
    Cassette backup: CA 107a
    Work number: ubmu0063_032_09
    Wesley, Charles
    Roll, Jordan, roll, arranged
    Duration: 2:27
    Cassette backup: CA 107b
    Work number: ubmu0063_032_10
    Sonata, horn, piano, op. 17, F major
    Performers: Stephen Seiffert, horn; Carlo Pinto, piano
    Duration: 14:26
    Cassette backup: CA 108
    Work number: ubmu0063_032_11
    Poulenc, Francis
    Elegie for Horn and piano
    Duration: 9:39
    Cassette backup: CA 109
    Work number: ubmu0063_032_12
    Chabrier, Emmanuel
    Larghetto Pour Cornet et piano
    Duration: 9:14
    Cassette backup: CA 110
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 17, January 25, 1967, 4 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 3-4, Reel 033-036)
    Work number: ubmu0063_033_01
    Bach, Johann Sebastian
    Suite, violoncello alone, no. 2, BWV 1008, D minor, arranged
    Duration: 18:34
    Cassette backup: CA 111
    Work number: ubmu0063_034_01
    Duo, viola, violoncello, Wo032, E-flat major
    Performers: Jean Dupouy, viola; Robert Martin, violoncello
    Duration: 8:16
    Cassette backup: CA 112
    Work number: ubmu0063_034_02
    Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus
    Duet, violin, viola, K. 423, G major
    Performers: Charles Haupt, violin; Jean Dupouy, viola; Robert Martin, violoncello
    Duration: 15:17
    Cassette backup: CA 113
    Work number: ubmu0063_035_01
    Trio, violin, viola, violoncello, op. 9, no. 3, C minor
    Duration: 23:44
    Cassette backup: CA 114
    Work number: ubmu0063_036_01
    Telemann, Georg Philipp
    Concerto, viola and string orchestra, G minor
    Performers: Jean Dupouy, viola; Charles Haupt, S. Lee Larrison, violins; Michele Gallien, viola; Robert Martin, violoncello; Makoto Michii, double bass; David Fuller, harpsichord
    Duration: 14:39
    Cassette backup: CA 115
    Work number: ubmu0063_036_02
    Concerto, viola and string orchestra, G minor. Allegro
    Cassette backup: CA 115a
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 18, February 1, 1967, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 4, Reel 037-038)
    Work number: ubmu0063_037_01
    Oster-Oratorium. Sinfonia
    Performers: Andrew White, oboe; David Fuller, harpsichord; Robert Martin, violoncello
    Duration: 5:24
    Cassette backup: CA 116
    Work number: ubmu0063_037_02
    Concerto, flute, oboe, bassoon, F. XII, no. 4, G minor
    Performers: Shaul Ben Meir, flute; Andrew White, oboe; David Fuller, harpsichord; Darlene Reynard, bassoon
    Duration: 10:50
    Cassette backup: CA 117
    Work number: ubmu0063_037_03
    Dutilleux, Henri
    Sonatina, flute, piano
    Performers: Shaul Ben Meir, flute; Carlo Pinto, piano
    Duration: 8:46
    Cassette backup: CA 118
    Work number: ubmu0063_038_01
    Quartet, oboe, strings, K. 368b (370), F major
    Performers: Andrew White, oboe; Charles Haupt, violin; Jean Dupouy, viola; Robert Martin, violoncello
    Duration: 13:41
    Cassette backup: CA 119
    Work number: ubmu0063_038_02
    Villa-Lobos, Heitor
    Bachianas Brasileiras No. 6
    Performers: Shaul Ben Meir, flute; Darlene Reynard, bassoon
    Cassette backup: CA 120
    Work number: ubmu0063_038_03
    Quantz, Johann Joachim
    Sonata, flute, oboe, continuo, C minor
    Performers: Shaul Ben Meir, flute; Andrew White, oboe; David Fuller, harpsichord; Robert Martin, violoncello
    Duration: 10:58
    Cassette backup: CA 121
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 19, February 22, 1967, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 4, Reel 039)
    Work number: ubmu0063_039_01
    Wrochem, Klaus von
    Altes Thema, neu Gestellt (1965)
    Performers: Klaus von Wrochem, S. Lee Larrison, violins; Robert Martin, violoncello
    Cassette backup: CA 122
    Work number: ubmu0063_039_02
    Musikalisches Opfer. Sonata, flute, violin, continuo, C minor
    Performers: Shaul Ben Meir, flute; Klaus von Wrochem, violin; David Fuller, harpsichord; Robert Martin, violoncello
    Duration: 20:11
    Cassette backup: CA 123
    Work number: ubmu0063_039_03
    Improvisation (1967)
    Performers: Klaus von Wrochem, violin; Joseph Romanowski, Mike Di Noto, technicians
    Duration: 7:48
    Cassette backup: CA 124
    Work number: ubmu0063_039_04
    Bartok, Bela
    Sonata, violin
    Performers: Klaus von Wrochem, violin
    Duration: 33:50
    Cassette backup: CA 125
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 20, March 5, 1967, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 4, Reel 040-041)
    Work number: ubmu0063_040_01
    Koussevitsky, Serge
    Concerto, double bass, op. 3, F# minor
    Performers: Makoto Michii, double bass; William Kothe, piano
    Duration: 18:09
    Cassette backup: CA 126
    Work number: ubmu0063_040_02
    Chanson Triste, op. 2
    Duration: 5:09
    Cassette backup: CA 127
    Work number: ubmu0063_040_03
    Valse Miniature, op. 1, no. 2
    Duration: 3:19
    Cassette backup: CA 128
    Work number: ubmu0063_041_01
    Septet, strings, winds, op. 20, E-flat major
    Performers: Paul Zonn, clarinet; Stephen Seiffert, horn; Darlene Reynard, bassoon; S. Lee Larrison, violin; Jean Dupouy, viola; Madalena Marx, violoncello; Makoto Michii, double bass
    Duration: 43:23
    Cassette backup: CA 129
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 22, April 5, 1967, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 4, Reel 042-043)
    Work number: ubmu0063_042_01
    Russell, William
    Three dance movements (1933)
    Performers: Edward Burnham, Lynn Harbold, John Rowland, Jan Williams, percussion
    Duration: 5:05
    Cassette backup: CA 139
    Work number: ubmu0063_042_02
    Fugue
    Duration: 4:34
    Cassette backup: CA 140
    Work number: ubmu0063_042_03
    Interactions
    Performers: Joseph Guarnieri, Michael Horwood, James Santella, Mark Schneider, Karen Shaver, William Thiele, percussion
    Duration: 6:59
    Cassette backup: CA 141
    Work number: ubmu0063_043_01
    Hassell, Jon
    Music for Vibraphone and Tape
    Performers: Edward Burnham, Jan Williams, vibraphones
    Duration: 9:52
    Cassette backup: CA 142
    Work number: ubmu0063_043_02
    Albright, William
    Tic
    Performers: Andrew White, saxophone; Edward Burnham, Jan Williams, percussion
    Duration: 14:10
    Cassette backup: CA 143
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 24, November 29, 1967, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 4, Reel 044-045)
    Work number: ubmu0063_044_01
    Childs, Barney
    Music for trombone and piano (1966)
    Performers: Stuart Dempster, trombone; Margaret Hassell, piano
    Duration: 8:50
    Cassette backup: CA 149
    Note: Engineer notes reordering on inserted program.
    Note: Presentation order changed from printed program - fix inventory
    Work number: ubmu0063_044_02
    Roque Alsina, Carlos
    Trio (1967)
    Performers: Stuart Dempster, trombone; Robert Martin, violoncello; Jan Williams, percussion
    Duration: 16:22
    Cassette backup: CA 150
    Work number: ubmu0063_045_01
    Blackboard piece with girls and loops (1967)
    Performers: Coni Burnham, Margaret Hassell, girls
    Duration: 18:47
    Cassette backup: CA 153
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 25, December 6, 1967, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 15 ips and 7 ½ ips (Box 4, Reel 046)
    Work number: ubmu0063_046_01
    Singer, Lawrence Raphael
    Unnamed composition for solo oboe
    Performers: Lawrence Singer, oboe
    Duration: 5:29
    Cassette backup: CA 154
    Work number: ubmu0063_046_02
    Newton, Lynn David
    What Good is a Trombone Player?
    Performers: Stuart Dempster, trombone
    Duration: 18:02
    Cassette backup: CA 155
    Work number: ubmu0063_046_03
    Rosenboom, David
    "The Brandy of the Damned" (1967)
    Performers: David Rosenboom, instrumental environment
    Duration: 15:34
    Cassette backup: CA 156
    Work number: ubmu0063_046_04
    Gaber, Harley
    Voce II (1964-65)
    Performers: Miriam Abramowitsch, soprano; David Shostac, alto flute; Jan Williams, percussion
    Duration: 11:08
    Cassette backup: CA 157
    Work number: ubmu0063_046_05
    Unknown
    Heroin (Velvet Underground cover). Introductory Lines, Waking, and Aluminum Foil Fantasy
    Performers: Time (David Rosenboom, Lynn David Newton, Richard Stanley, Thomas G. McFaul)
    Duration: 44:19
    Cassette backup: CA 158
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 26, January 13, 1968, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 5, Reel 047-048)
    Work number: ubmu0063_047_01
    Handel, Georg Friedrich
    Sonata, flute, continuo, op. 1, no. 7, C major
    Performers: David Shostac, flute; David Fuller, harpsichord; Robert Martin, violoncello
    Duration: 10:48
    Cassette backup: CA 159
    Work number: ubmu0063_047_02
    Scarlatti, Domenico
    Sonata, harpsichord, L. 352, arranged
    Performers: Jonathan Marcus, guitar
    Duration: 3:39
    Cassette backup: CA 160
    Work number: ubmu0063_047_03
    Frescobaldi, Girolamo Alessandro
    Air and Variations "La Frescobalda"
    Duration: 5:46
    Cassette backup: CA 161
    Work number: ubmu0063_047_04
    Serenade, flute, violin, viola, op. 25, D major
    Performers: David Shostac, flute; Frank Preuss, violin; Jesse Levine, viola
    Duration: 27:51
    Cassette backup: CA 162
    Work number: ubmu0063_048_01
    Ibert, Jacques
    Entr'acte
    Performers: David Shostac, flute; Jonathan Marcus, guitar
    Duration: 5:22
    Cassette backup: CA 163
    Work number: ubmu0063_048_02
    Prelude, guitar, no. 4
    Duration: 4:29
    Cassette backup: CA 164
    Work number: ubmu0063_048_03
    Etude, guitar, no. 7
    Duration: 4:22
    Cassette backup: CA 165
    Work number: ubmu0063_048_04
    Quartet, flute, strings, K. 285, D major
    Performers: David Shostac, flute; Donald Downs, violin; Jesse Levine, viola; Robert Martin, violoncello
    Duration: 15:37
    Cassette backup: CA 166
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 27, January 24, 1968, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 5, Reel 049-050)
    Work number: ubmu0063_049_01
    Schumann, Robert
    Dichterliebe
    Performers: Miriam Abramowitsch, soprano; David Del Tredici, piano
    Duration: 31:17
    Cassette backup: CA 167
    Work number: ubmu0063_050_01
    If my complaints could passions move
    Performers: Miriam Abramowitsch, soprano; Jonathan Marcus, lute
    Duration: 4:58
    Cassette backup: CA 168
    Work number: ubmu0063_050_02
    Go, christall teares
    Cassette backup: CA 169
    Work number: ubmu0063_050_03
    Sorrow, sorrow, stay
    Duration: 3:16
    Cassette backup: CA 170
    Work number: ubmu0063_050_04
    Away with these selfe loving lads
    Duration: 2:05
    Cassette backup: CA 171
    Work number: ubmu0063_050_05
    Del Tredici, David
    I hear an army
    Performers: Miriam Abramowitsch, soprano; Donald Downs, violin; Frank Preuss, violin; Jesse Levine, viola; Robert Martin, violoncello
    Duration: 10:33
    Cassette backup: CA 172
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 28, January 31, 1968, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 5, Reel 051-052)
    Work number: ubmu0063_051_01
    Song of Queztecoatl (1943)
    Performers: Jan Williams, Edward Burnham, Lynn Harbold, John Rowland, percussion
    Cassette backup: CA 173
    Work number: ubmu0063_051_02
    Inventions on a Motive (1955)
    Duration: 14:13
    Cassette backup: CA 174
    Work number: ubmu0063_051_03
    To That Predestined Dancing Place (1967)
    Duration: 10:35
    Cassette backup: CA 175
    Work number: ubmu0063_052_01
    Moran, Robert Leonard
    Elegant Journey with Stopping Points of Interest (1965)
    Cassette backup: CA 176
    Work number: ubmu0063_052_02
    She is Asleep (1943)
    Duration: 4:35
    Cassette backup: CA 177
    Work number: ubmu0063_052_03
    Duration: 18:49
    Cassette backup: CA 178
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 29, February 22, 1968, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 5, Reel 053-054)
    Work number: ubmu0063_053_01
    Behrman, David
    Wave Train (1966)
    Performers: David Behrman, Gordon Mumma, pianos
    Duration: 20:15
    Cassette backup: CA 179
    Work number: ubmu0063_053_02
    Two pianos (1957)
    Duration: 9:56
    Cassette backup: CA 180
    Work number: ubmu0063_054_01
    Ashley, Robert
    Frogs (1967)
    Duration: 26:06
    Cassette backup: CA 181
    Work number: ubmu0063_054_02
    Mumma, Gordon
    Hornpipe (1967)
    Duration: 12:42
    Cassette backup: CA 182
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 30, February 28, 1968, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 5, Reel 055-056)
    Work number: ubmu0063_055_01
    Frohne, Vincent
    Three Studies for Clarinet Alone (1960)
    Performers: Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet
    Duration: 5:08
    Cassette backup: CA 184
    Work number: ubmu0063_055_02
    Debussy, Claude
    Arabesques, piano, arranged
    Performers: Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Carlos Roque Alsina, piano
    Duration: 8:43
    Cassette backup: CA 185
    Work number: ubmu0063_055_03
    Smith, William Overton
    Five pieces for Clarinet Alone (1958)
    Duration: 7:24
    Cassette backup: CA 186
    Work number: ubmu0063_056_01
    Quintet, clarinet, strings, op. 115, B minor
    Performers: Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Frank Preuss, Donald Downs, violins, Jesse Levine, viola; Robert Martin, violoncello
    Duration: 39:20
    Cassette backup: CA 187
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 31, March 24, 1968, 3 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 5-6, Reel 057-059)
    Work number: ubmu0063_057_01
    Sonata, 2 violins, continuo, B. 68, no. 8, arranged
    Performers: Robert Martin, David Crowley, violoncellos; Carlos Roque Alsina, piano
    Cassette backup: CA 188
    Work number: ubmu0063_057_02
    Boccherini, Luigi
    Sonata, violoncello, continuo, G. 4, A major
    Performers: Robert Martin, violoncello; Carlos Roque Alsina, piano
    Cassette backup: CA 189
    Work number: ubmu0063_058_01
    Sonata, violoncello, piano, op. 102, no. 2, D major
    Duration: 18:20
    Cassette backup: CA 190
    Work number: ubmu0063_059_01
    Fantasiestucke, violoncello, piano, op. 73
    Duration: 11:49
    Cassette backup: CA 191
    Work number: ubmu0063_059_02
    Sonata, violoncello, piano
    Cassette backup: CA 192
    Work number: ubmu0063_059_03
    Bloch, Ernest
    "Prayer" for violoncello and strings
    Performers: Robert Martin, violoncello; Frank Preuss, Donald Downs, violins; Jesse Levine, viola; Makoto Michii, double bass
    Duration: 4:54
    Cassette backup: CA 193
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 32, April 17, 1968, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 6, Reel 060-061)
    Work number: ubmu0063_060_01
    Webern, Anton von
    Konzert, op. 24 (1934)
    Performers: David Shostac, flute; Lawrence Singer, oboe; Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Jon Hassell, trumpet; William Lane, horn; Stuart Dempster, trombone; Charles Haupt, violin; David Rosenboom, viola; Margaret Hassell, piano; Carlos Roque Alsina, conductor
    Duration: 10:05
    Cassette backup: CA 194
    Work number: ubmu0063_060_02
    Variationen, op. 27 (1936)
    Performers: Carlos Roque Alsina, piano
    Duration: 7:43
    Cassette backup: CA 195
    Work number: ubmu0063_060_03
    Drei Kleine Stucke, op. 11 (1914)
    Duration: 5:21
    Cassette backup: CA 196
    Work number: ubmu0063_060_04
    Funf Lieder, op. 4 (1909)
    Performers: Miriam Abramowitsch, soprano; Carlos Roque Alsina, piano
    Duration: 9:02
    Cassette backup: CA 197
    Work number: ubmu0063_060_05
    Octandre
    Performers: David Shostac, flute, piccolo; Lawrence Singer, oboe; Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet, piccolo clarinet; Darlene Reynard, bassoon; Jon Hassell, trumpet; William Lane, horn; Stuart Dempster, trombone; Makoto Michii, double bass; Carlos Roque Alsina, conductor
    Duration: 10:15
    Cassette backup: CA 198
    Work number: ubmu0063_061_01
    Ives, Charles Edward
    Sonata, piano, no. 2. The Alcotts. Thoreau
    Performers: Carlos Roque Alsina, piano; David Shostac, flute
    Duration: 17:08
    Cassette backup: CA 199
    Work number: ubmu0063_061_02
    Maderna, Bruno
    Le Rire
    Performers: Tape realized by the composer (only first 2 minutes recorded)
    Duration: 6:13
    Cassette backup: CA 200
    Work number: ubmu0063_061_03
    Textes 1967
    Performers: Miriam Abramowitsch, soprano; David Shostac, flute; Jon Hassell, trumpet; Stuart Dempster, trombone; Jan Williams, percussion; Carlos Roque Alsina, piano; David Rosenboom, violin; Robert Martin, violoncello; Makoto Michii, double bass; Jerry McBride, conductor
    Duration: 28:57
    Cassette backup: CA 201
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 33, October 18, 1968, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 15 ips (Box 6, Reel 062-063)
    Work number: ubmu0063_062_01
    Sonata, viola da gamba, continuo, BWV 1028, D major
    Performers: Marijke Verberne, violoncello; Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 16:02
    Cassette backup: CA 202
    Work number: ubmu0063_062_02
    Performers: Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Marijke Verberne, violoncello; Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 21:42
    Cassette backup: CA 203
    Work number: ubmu0063_063_01
    Krenek, Ernest
    Trio for Clarinet, Violin, and Violoncello (1946)
    Performers: Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Charles Haupt, violin; Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 7:47
    Cassette backup: CA 204
    Work number: ubmu0063_063_02
    Dahl, Ingolf
    Concerto a tre for clarinet, violin, and violoncello (1947)
    Performers: Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Charles Haupt, violin; Marijke Verberne, violoncello
    Duration: 20:00
    Cassette backup: CA 205
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 34, November 18, 1968, 2 10-inch reels; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 6, Reel 064-065)
    Work number: ubmu0063_064-065_01
    Austin, Larry and Lunetta, Stanley George
    Two Man Show (Multi-media events). Parts 1 and 2
    Performers: Larry Austin, Stanley Lunetta
    Duration: 1:20:11
    Cassette backup: CA 206
    Note: One work divided over two tapes
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 35, December 2, 1968, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 6, Reel 066)
    Work number: ubmu0063_066_01
    Cantata no. 202: Weichet nur, betrubte Schatten!
    Performers: Gwendolin Sims, soprano; Lawrence Singer, oboe; Frank Preuss, Darrell Berg, violin; Jesse Levine, viola; Marijke Verberne, violoncello; Thomas Coleman, double bass; Melvin Strauss, conductor
    Duration: 19:46
    Cassette backup: CA 207
    Work number: ubmu0063_066_02
    Bella mia fiamma, addoi! K. 528
    Performers: Gwendolin Sims, soprano; Melvin Strauss, piano
    Duration: 8:04
    Cassette backup: CA 208
    Work number: ubmu0063_066_03
    Songs: Suleika, D. 720, Liebhaber in allen Gestalten, D. 558, Du liebst mich nicht, D. 756, Seligkeit, D. 433, Gretchen am Spinnrade, D. 118
    Duration: 21:04
    Cassette backup: CA 210-215
    Work number: ubmu0063_066_04
    Bachianas brasileiras No. 5
    Performers: Gwendolin Sims, soprano; Bruce Cramer, Cheryl Grant, Bernard Henderson, Mary Lane, Madalena Marx, Suzanne Mustard, Mary Sue Payne, Marijke Verberne, violoncelli; Melvin Strauss, conductor
    Duration: 12:29
    Cassette backup: CA 209
  - Creative Associates Recitals no. 37, February 15, 1969, 1 10-inch reel; ½-track stereo, 7.5 ips (Box 6, Reel 067)
    Work number: ubmu0063_067_01
    Toccata, harpsichord, BWV 914, E minor
    Performers: Yuji Takahashi, piano
    Duration: 9:17
    Cassette backup: CA 220
    Work number: ubmu0063_067_02
    Berg, Alban
    Sonata, piano, op. 1
    Duration: 12:30
    Cassette backup: CA 221